https://www.pcpools.com/service/privacy/

Above Ground Pool Liner Accessories
In Ground Pool Liners (Custom)
Recently Viewed
You have not viewed any products recently.
Home . Customer Service . Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
At Pc Pools, we respect your concerns about privacy. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this web site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone, but can share such information within the Pc Pools’ family of companies. We gather online customer information to improve the content of our web site, to enhance your online shopping experience and for marketing and promotional purposes. We collect information from you when you purchase a product from us.
The information you provide upon registering to purchase includes general facts necessary for us to complete your order including your name, mailing address, shipping addresses, email address, and credit card number. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Your credit card number is privileged information and will at no time be shared with a third party. Your online account information is stored and maintained in a secure location separate from this web site.
Wherever we collect sensitive information from our customers, such as your credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online we also protect your information offline. Only Pc Pools’ employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Search
Expert Advice
About Us
News
Testimonials
Resources
Blog
Pool Library
